<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bios on Michal Koperski, PhD</title>
    <link>http://mkoperski.com/bio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bios on Michal Koperski, PhD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Michal Koperski</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="http://mkoperski.com/bio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://mkoperski.com/bio/08_tplx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkoperski.com/bio/08_tplx/</guid>
      <description>From Aug 2018 I am a Research Scientist at Tooploox.
 I am working on deep neural networks models for object recognition, detection on images and videos, I am advising junior scientists, I am working on a research project on incremental and multimodal learning (check our new publication), I am working on code transfer to our industrial partners.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://mkoperski.com/bio/09_inria_postdoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkoperski.com/bio/09_inria_postdoc/</guid>
      <description>From Dec 2017 until Jul 2018 I was a Post-doc at INRIA (STARS).
 I worked on deep neural networks with spatio-temporal attention for action recognition, I worked on real-time action detection, I worked on technology transfer to industrial partners I published 6 scientific papers.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://mkoperski.com/bio/10_inria.phd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkoperski.com/bio/10_inria.phd/</guid>
      <description>From Feb 2014 until Nov 2017 I was PhD Student at INRIA (STARS). During my PhD I:
 I proposed, implemented and validated several methods for action recognition and action detection, I published 9 scientific papers, The code of the proposed methods was successfully transferred to Toyota.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://mkoperski.com/bio/11_disney_intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkoperski.com/bio/11_disney_intern/</guid>
      <description>From Jan 2016 until Apr 2016 I was a Research Intern at Disney Research Pittsburgh. I was working on codebook representation for People Re-Identification. During my internship:
 I published 1 scientific paper, 1 patent request was filed.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://mkoperski.com/bio/12_inria_intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkoperski.com/bio/12_inria_intern/</guid>
      <description>From Apr 2013 until Sep 2013 I was Research Intern at INRIA (STARS). I was working on multimodal RGB-D representation for action recognition. During my internship I:
 proposed, implemented and validated new RGB-D descriptor for action recognition, I published 1 scientific paper.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://mkoperski.com/bio/13_put/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://mkoperski.com/bio/13_put/</guid>
      <description>From Apr 2010 until Apr 2012 I was Research Engineer at Poznan University of Technology (IDSS). I was working on automatic bird species detection, using machine learning. During the project I:
 implemented and validated bird species detection system for mobile devices (ARM). I published 1 book chapter  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>